Hello Hello friends how are you all I
hope you all are doing very well
and having a lot of fun, by seeing the title of today's video
you all must have understood that that is
why we made today's video,
I was getting a lot of comments asking
how did you do it, how did it happen, it is
very important for me, I
need a lot of you, those of you who
want this video to be made on Monday itself, are
commenting, they will also get
help and with this you can be
in my video bye-bye till then
please
tell my Gupta from whoever side what kind of
documents we
needed, what was the rest of the resort, how was the
experience, I will
tell you later, Hello friends, as I told you all that
today I am going to share my experience,
how we travelled,
now we covered it, we reached there and have
appointed two members
and you are from India, Astra Zenica
Djokovic person whose name is Vijay  Raghavan Rupees
people can't take it, you can come here I have asked
you to update the system, if there is any festival
or withdrawal like war breaks out then I have to
subscribe and the next day it takes the
previous appointment, on that
basis you can enter here, the
benefit of which is that
after coming to Saudi Arabia
you would not have applied for the current time period on World S,
but when we had appointed that, I had
not applied and when we came back from there, we had
not started, so I had subscribed and
now I will share some information on the screen, first of all we should subscribe
and subscribe and
subscribe, if you are appointed by an insurance company
for Reliance, I will
also share some information for the society in the question box,
that before you go,
take this quarter inch, you will think that by going to
Malviya, we will take this quarter inch, then you
can fill the problem that it was
planned with us that we
went to massage and took insurance,
in an insurance, we got momentum in a resort, so
friends please loot school
should subscribe, second thing is that
you should not get hospitalized due to war
But if your test is found positive, then
before leaving you will have to
follow there again. It
is necessary to appoint him in the hospital. The
next person does not need to go to the hospital,
for that you need hotel accommodation,
subscription, lunch should also be there or
not. If there is any
difference, when you
select those people, then here
you must tell him that you want it, if it is
very important then definitely keep this thing in
mind, subscribe, you
can add any and subscribe and
apart from this, two resorts are very famous, very
good option for appointment there,
subscribe and this is uninhabited, the
government alone in all states, in these there,
many people live here,
coat and here people live less, so let's go
here, we were gang-raped and they took
us very urgently, so
subscribe, I will give their link
in the description box, these people
want it and subscribe
in the subscribe, so if you want to get it done from them, then
you can get it done, that is,
our love inch mark, so we have a
lot  If it took more time then we had become domestic from the airport
under international airport,
here we had traveled to our department
domestic airport, so the
typing on this helped us a lot,
so you can get it done from them, if you are
ready to get a place in Tubelight India and if you are
ready to leave home then
definitely visit the video subscribe the driver said that the
problem of those middle aged people is that they have children, so you must have left
from home as much as you want that there are a
lot of problems with the children,
so we faced a lot of problems in all this timing
and but one thing is that we were living in another
country, we could do this,
like we could not go anywhere, here
in Bahrain, where are you subscribing right now, I do
n't know that it is very hot here
and one very important thing is that if by chance the
vaccine is not available
before leaving then you should be appointed in Saudi, so
subscribe
now you can type your phone from So Diya Holidays website,
if you are
with family, you must be subscribed,
for this it is necessary that young people are appointed,
these people  If you agree that you should not take it then
you must take it in any case, so if you have
insurance on the youth then there will be a
lot of problem in traveling, we will inspect it, there were a
lot of problems, hence we will reach at this time,
if you have front arm hole
then you should remember the terminal appointment and this was done that if you
subscribe to the war of one and a half inch by the youth then you
can subscribe to the village, for
example, if you
cannot travel till the appointed date, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen or fifteen hundred, then you can do it, so keep in
mind
that whenever you leave from India,
after leaving India, you will have to calculate the subscription you need,
if you do not want to take it then it would be
better to
subscribe to other tips tomorrow, so
friends, you should keep here that the war
website appointment and after that,
we will keep this one and a half inch and people inside it, for
this reason here in the contra voucher,
like the
vegetables of A, in this entire travel, you
can assume that one person is more, then the
total accused  If you
can subscribe
to this then it was closed
with a medical lab in India, they had
stopped travel so that we cannot do Indian style
flights were cancelled and we were
appointed for this, now let's talk,
we were given below results, so
we did not face any problem, so we cannot go from room to
food, lunch and dinner,
if you can write and you
want to take it from 1 and
subscribe,
these goods have a lot of differences, if your
budget is low then you can buy from this,
now I will tell you,
subscribe to us during lunch time, we both did
not do it at all, we used to do it and it was
closed till 10 o'clock, I don't know about
other systems, but if you must share it with yourself, then
definitely keep namkeen and snacks here, the
system was very good, you will get loot
and all the sweets are
available there, there is no problem in eating,
just a little bit of timing, if
you are defence personnel, if you click at lunch time then
that is fine  There is no
problem but you should get a little bit of
timing from us because after 2 o'clock we
block questions and remind
friends, you should stop it, you cannot get treatment here after 2 o'clock,
you will have to go and take lunch break and send it within the timing of the vitamin, just
send this one, I felt that there should not be any timing
because if you are on one line then you should
get food and drink decisions, disco disco hours, so this is known, extra stock
cannot be taken, you cannot go outside, hence it is
not right
and one more thing if you are coming to Saudi and it is going to be
7.5, after coming to Saudi, I will
meet you, bring ready-to-eat food with you
because many times it happens that
you will get ready-to-eat food here,
which you do not know, the
problem I used to have, I
could not say much to show you, and non-veg
is available, if Khojeli Baghwa now you
cannot always eat Naagin, definitely carry your well-planned tweets,
carry snacks with you,
gift for Madihan, I will try more  It seemed
and at least we started facing a lot of problems with
it but Yash landing and edition has been
muted,
Olive News has gone, so you guys
supported us a lot, we came through Maldives, due to which
this became our first international travel, Yasmin
laughed a lot with us and this and the cloth, in this
this is also the entire portion of our rice, she is also going to
share her experience,
tell me how to apply the garlic you told me to
our face, hello friends,
I am leaving, with this I end this video, I hope
you all have got the
answers to all your questions, so with this
I end today's video, you all liked everything
very much, you all
understood everything correctly, if you have any
doubt, if you feel like asking
us, you can ask us by commenting in the comment section
and if you like it then
give a like and if you are new to the channel and
subscribe, ok guys, I will meet you with a
new look, with a new beginning, take
care of yourself, stay happy, bye bye tata bye-bye Jhal